Guide to the David A. Clarke papers, 1974-1997 MS2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Part 2 (donated 1997-2000), 1974-1997; Series 2; 129 Linear Feet
  - Subject files, 1977-1997; Series 2 Subseries 2
    - Media info, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Media watch, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Medicaid, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Medical providers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Medical Research Institution, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Medicine, Board of, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Medlantic Healthcare Group, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Meeting with members, 1994 December 18; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Meeting with members, 1994 December 15; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Meeting with members, 1994 December 20; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Meeting with Professor Richard B. Stewart, 1989 February 03; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Meeting with supporters of Office on Latino Affairs, 1994 December 13; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Meetings and hearings, 1977-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Meetings and hearings, 1983-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Mega-cities, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Member Conciliations, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Memo to committee chairs, 1994 December 08; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Memo to members, 1994 December 22; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Memo to Members re: Standard and Poors, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Memorable readings, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda, legal and informational, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Memorandum -- legal, extra copies [handguns], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Memos, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Memos -- gun classification, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Messages, telephone numbers, addresses, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Metro advertising, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Metro Police Department Investigations Division, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Metro Yellow Line at Gallery Place, 1983 April 30; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Metropolitan Police Department (firearms), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Metropolitan Police Department manual, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Metropolitan Washington Council/AFL-CIO B10-307 (Displaced Workers Protection Act of 1993), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Meyers, Tedson J., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Michigan Park Citizens Association, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Miles, James Bernard, Esq., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Miller, Charles, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Ministers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Ministers' breakfast re: death penalty/executions, 1983 July 08; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Ministers list, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Ministers, June 13, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Misfires, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Mitchell, Keith, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Model Transit -- An Alternative Parking Policy for the District of Columbia, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Modern torts list, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Montgomery County Council, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Monumental Core, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Mooney, Sally, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Moore memo re: FY 1995 Budget Spending Plan, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Moore, Jeffrey, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Moore, Rev. Jerry A. Jr., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Morris Mason, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Mortgage Bankers Association of America, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Mortgaged Future, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Mortgaged Future, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Mortgaged Future, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Multiyear Spending Reduction and Support Act of 1994, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Municipal primary, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Myles Glasgow, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Myles Glasgow and Edith Maeda, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Nagoya City Assembly paperweight, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Nataka G. Wilson Nomination, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Nathanson, James, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - National Association for Equal Opportunity in Higher Education, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - National Association for Equal Opportunity in Higher Education, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - National Baptist Convention, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - National Beauty Culturists' League, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - National Capital Development Corp. (Sports Arena), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - National Capital Development Corporation, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - National Capital Planning Commission, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty Conference, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty Conference, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty Conference, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty Conference, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty Conference, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty Conference, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty fundraiser, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - National Conference of State Legislators, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - National Funeral Directors and Morticians' Association, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - National Guard, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - National Impact/Action, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - National League of Cities, Atlanta, GA, 1989 November 25; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - National League of Cities, Congress of Cities, San Antonio, 1986 November 29; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Natural and Artificial Gas Revenue Tax Amendment Act of 1996, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - NCADP, Dallas, Texas, 1988 November 18; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - NCSL Conference, Reno, Nevada, 1988 July 23; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Neighborhood Legal Services Program, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Neighborhood Partnership, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Neighbors Ink, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - New Bethel Baptist Church/Boy Scouts of America, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - New hires, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - New Republic, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - New York Avenue Presbyterian Church, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - News articles, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - News articles, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - News articles, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - News articles, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - news articles [death penalty], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - News clips, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - News releases, 1982 July - 1982 December; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - News releases, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - News releases, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - Newsletter, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Newsletters, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - NLC, Boston, Mass., 1988 December 03; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - North American Telecommunications (Protest Letter), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Norton, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Notebook, 1972-1974; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Notes, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Notes, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Notes, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - notes, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Notes, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Notes, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - notes [death penalty], Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Notes, meeting with Norton and Barry, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Notes/promises, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Notes: 1, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - November 12 Coalition, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 43)
    - NRA [National Rifle Association], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Nuclear freeze meeting, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 44)
    - Numbers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Numbers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Numbers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Numbers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - N'Zinga Al-Shams, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 23)
    - O.M., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Oath of Office, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Office, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Office budget, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Office Manual, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Office of Campaign Finance Hearing -- Friends of Dave Clarke, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Office of International Business, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Omnibus Budget Support Act, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Omnibus Criminal Justice Reform Amendment Act of 1994, B10-98, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - One Stop Center for International Trade, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Operations, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Opinions of the General Counsel, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Opposition, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - opposition [death penalty], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - OPS reports, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Organization of Chinese Americans, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Organizational materials [death penalty], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Originals, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Oshinaika, Marcia R., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Other organizations [death penalty], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Other organizations [death penalty], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Other states and cities, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Others' efforts, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Others' efforts [death penalty], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Our brief [Atkinson v. DC BOEE], 1991; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Our brief [Atkinson v. DC BOEE], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Our Mortgaged Future, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Outplacement Service (General Employment Market), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Oxford House, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Pam Johnson, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Parking tax increase info, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Parlours (1 of 2), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Parlours (2 of 2), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Parting, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Pastor Hicks, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Paul Lutzker, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Pay, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Pay raise questions, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Pay raises, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Peace Council, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Peat Marwick LLp, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Pederson and Freedman, LLP, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Peebles, Don, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue closing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Pension legislation, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Pension reform, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Pensions, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - People for Pro-Tenant Council, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - PEPCO PAC, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 45)
    - Personal notes, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Personnel, D.C. Emergency Rulemaking, 1993 September 13; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Personnel, Office of, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Petitions, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Photograph: Ribbon-cutting at the Washington Convention Center, 1982 December 10; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Photographs of Clarke with politicians and dignitaries, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Photographs of Thailand and Turkey, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Pic Bill (David Hall), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Director reports, Agenda, Minutes, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Director reports, Agenda, Minutes, 1972 January-May; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Director reports, Agenda, Minutes, 1972 April-December; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Director reports, Agenda, Minutes, 1971 January-May; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Director reports, Agenda, Minutes, 1971 June-December; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Director reports, Agenda, Minutes, 1970 July-December; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Director reports, Agenda, Minutes, 1970 February-June; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Election, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Evaluations, 1971-1972; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Financial reports, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) General, 1973; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) General, 1972; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) General, 1971; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) General, 1970; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Newspapers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) pamphlets, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Personnel/Board lists, staff structure, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Police procedures and operations commission, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Police procedures and operations commission, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) projects, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) projects, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) propaganda, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Proposals, grants, bylaws, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Proposals, grants, bylaws, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Proposals, grants, bylaws, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Proposals, grants, bylaws, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Proposals, grants, bylaws, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Proposals, grants, bylaws, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Pilot District Project (PDP) Proposals, grants, bylaws, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Planned Parenthood, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Planning, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Plans and strategies, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Pledge named [death penalty], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Plymouth Congregational Church, 1983 May 09; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 46)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, affidavits, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 18)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Alexander Perez and other defendants, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 17)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Allen Rogers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 15)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, congressional bills, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, correspondence, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 25)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Dennis Maloney, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 19)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Duty list, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 21)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Gibson, Montez, Ramirez, Wulbert, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Gonzales, Espinoza, Wulbert, King, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, jail inmates, index of criminal cases and visit hours memo, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 16)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, list of attorneys, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, lists of persons arrested from the Poor Person's Campaign, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Margo Ruth George and Jeff Lewis, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 22)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, mass arrest material litigation, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 23)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, miscellaneous, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, miscellaneous, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, news clippings, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Office memoranda, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Personal memoranda, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 14)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 18)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 19)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, exhibit file, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, photographs, exhibit file, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 21)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, receipts, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Reese W. James folder, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Richard David Cole, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Poor People's Campaign -- Legal work, Ronnie Ray Johnson, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 137, Folder 6)